KAROLYN SEREDICK

Brookhaven, GA 30319

Phone: 815-900-0328 | Email: Kseredick95@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/karolyn-seredick-227617195/ Github:

https://www.github.com/Kseredick95 | Portfolio: https://kseredick95.github.io/Profile/portfolio.html

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web developer with education from Georgia Institute of Technology. Experience in Java, Javascript, HTML5, Express, Mysql, MongoDB, Node.js, React and more. Excellent at multitasking, always meeting deadline requirements, and exceptional problem-solving at all levels of coding. Strong leadership qualities and team player. I am enthusiastic to show my skills in creative solutions for both server and user side development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Java, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5, React Applications: Node.js, Express, MySQL, Bootstrap, MongoDB

PROJECTS

CampfireStories | https://github.com/Kseredick95/CampfireStories https://campfirestories.herokuapp.com

- Online story game with friends. Create an account, pick a theme and make your choice in single player mode or create your own story with friends.
- The profile page displays a person's username and ending achievements.
- My responsibilities were to handle the database and password encryption for user accounts, assist in story database handling, create the server, edit api and html routing, took a leadership role in organization of team-members and their responsibilities.
- MongoDB, Node.js, Express, React, Bootstrap, Mongoose-Bcrypt, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Hourly | https://github.com/Kseredick95/hourly-project | https://hourly-app.herokuapp.com/

- Project management application for those working as a team.
- Add in team members, create a project and assign tasks. Edit to change from not started/ in progress/ completed.
- My responsibilities were to handle the database for projects, create the server, edit routing, populating the project homepage and team members page.
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, mySQL, Node.is, Express, Bootstrap

ClientClock | https://github.com/kseredick95/Code-wizards | https://kseredick95.github.io/Code-wizards/

- This is a timer application for accountants, lawyers or other bill by the hour positions.
- Enter in the billing rate, enter or select a name and begin the timer. Stop timer and hit the save button to populate a summary/invoice page.
- My responsibilities were to create the HTML, drop-down menus with names, debug copied names from appearing, saving client lists in local storage with their assigned information.
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

Store Manager/Assistant Manager Spencer's/Spirit Halloween

2017- 2020

MaryEsther/Destin, FL, Duluth, GA

Designated animatronic and display constructor/troubleshooter for Greater Atlanta locations. Trained new District/Store managers and associates, achieved sales goals, maintained store appearance, and updated visuals/walls/etc, communicated with staff and encouraged them to reach goals. *Key Accomplishments:*

- Achieved and exceeded store donation goals over 140% (Spirit Halloween).
- Exceeded sales plan by over 40% (Spirit Halloween).
- Survived two hurricanes, including hurricane Michael.

Shift Lead 2019– 2020 Smoothie King Buckhead, GA

Provided great customer service, trained staff, maintained a clean environment, scheduled workers and handled inventory.

Cafe Lead 2016– 2017 Books-a-Million Destin, FL

Ordered supplies and food, kept all retail signage current, maintained and cleaned the café, provided excellent customer service, trained new employees and maintained equipment

EDUCATION

Web-Development Certificate: Georgia Technical Institute, Atlanta, GA

Associates in Arts with Honors: Northwest Florida State College, Niceville, FL

High School Diploma: Prairie Ridge Highschool, Crystal Lake, IL